Preliminary Inventory to the Mark Starr Papers TAM.019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Second Accession, II
  - Clippings: General; Clippings: Socialist Party, 1932 Elections; Clippings: Cuba; Clippings: U2 Incident, Presidential Election; Documents, Miscellaneous; American Civil Liberties Union; White House Conference: Correspondence and Other Related Material; Labor Management Conference Program; Second Corning Conference, 1930s-1950s; 1932; 1960-1962; 1960; 1930s-1950s; 1933; 1955; 1949; 1961 (Box 36)
  - Clippings; Correspondence: General, 1920s, 1952-1954, 1968; 1952-1954 (Box 37)
  - Personal Documents (Fliers, Invitations to Events, Itineraries, Personal Notes); Correspondence with Milton Elson, 1959-1965; 1970 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence; Brookwood Class Notes (typed and handwritten); Manuscripts by Mark Starr; ILGWU; LID, 1947-1973; 1928-1934; 1940s-1950s; 1937-1972; 1959 (Box 39)
  - Labor Jokes, Labor Novels, Labor Songs, Labor Poems; Miscellaneous Documents; Planned Parenthood (Birth Control), 1930s-1950s; 1930s-1950s; 1940s-1950s (Box 40)
  - Handwritten, typed, or printed Manuscripts of Speeches, Talks, and Articles, and some Clippings by Mark Starr; on British Labor Movement, US Trade Unions, Workers' Education, Teaching Methods, History, Economic Crisis and World War, 1920s-1942 (Box 41)
  - Handwritten, typed, or printed Manuscripts of Speeches, Talks, and Articles by Mark Starr; on British Labor Movement, US Trade Unions, Workers' Education, Teaching Methods, History, ILGWU, 1943-1949 (Box 42)
  - Handwritten, typed, or printed Manuscripts of Speeches, Talks, and Articles by Mark Starr; on British Labor Movement, US Trade Unions, Workers' Education, Teaching Methods, History, ILGWU, 1950-1954 (Box 43)
  - Handwritten, typed, or printed Manuscripts of Speeches, Talks, and Articles by Mark Starr; on British Labor Movement, US Trade Unions, Workers' Education, Teaching Methods, History, ILGWU, 1955-1958 (Box 44)
  - Handwritten, typed, or printed Manuscripts of Speeches, Talks, and Articles by Mark Starr; on British Labor Movement, US Trade Unions, Workers' Education, Teaching Methods, History, ILGWU, Peace, 1958-1974, undated (Box 45)
  - Mark Starr's Diaries and Yearbooks, 1949-1956 (Box 46)
  - Mark Starr's Diaries and Yearbooks, 1961-1969 (Box 47)
  - Mark Starr's Diaries and Yearbooks, 1957-1970 (Box 48)